Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
Douglas Menuez photography collection
1986-2006
MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
130.0 Linear feet (206 manuscript boxes, 104 flat boxes; 345,000 negatives/slides; 5 CD-ROMs)
Contains photographic materials, including prints, contact sheets, negatives and slides, relating to Menuez's documentation of major Silicon Valley companies, as well as to fine art book projects, photo essays and photo shoots for newspapers, magazines, advertising campaigns, annual reports and other commissioned work.
Menuez, Doug
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
The following boxes containing negatives are CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes:
Series 3: Boxes 1-7 - Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 1.
Series 5: Boxes 28-49, 55 - Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 5, Subseries 1. Jobs or Series 1, Subseries 1. Jobs (for Farallon).
Series 6: Box 2 - Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 6, Subseries 1 and 2.
The following boxes containing electronic media are CLOSED to researchers:
Series 4: Box 1 - Materials on CD-ROM may require 2-4 weeks for reformatting. Hard drive is CLOSED to researchers, but the contents are available via Stanford's Image Gallery (http://collections.stanford.edu/images/bin/page?forward=home).
Series 8: Boxes CM-1 and CM-2 - Materials on CDs may require 2-4 weeks for reformatting.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Douglas Menuez, 2004 (Accession 2004-060); 2005 (Accession 2005-126); 2006 (Accession 2006-207); 2007 (Accession 2007-081); 2008 (Accessions 2008-118 and 2008-179); 2010 (Accession 2010-209); 2011 (Accession 2011-132) and 2012 (2012-123).
Biography
Award-winning documentary photographer Douglas Menuez was born in Texas in 1957. He studied art and photography at the San Francisco Art Institute and San Francisco State University, and began his varied career shooting first for the Washington Post in 1981 followed by Time, Newsweek, Life, People, USA Today, Fortune Magazine and many other publications worldwide over the past twenty-five years. He’s covered major news stories including the famine in Ethiopia, the destruction of the Amazon, the AIDS crisis, drug wars, presidential campaigns, the Olympics, five Super Bowls and the World Series. His portraits of key figures range from Mother Teresa and Robert Redford, to President Clinton and Bill Gates.
Throughout the 1980s and 1990s, Menuez pursued a long-term project documenting the rise of Silicon Valley behind the scenes. With unprecedented access to almost every major technology company, including Apple, Adobe, Sun Microsystems, NeXT Inc and others, he covered digital pioneers such as Steve Jobs, Andy Grove, John Warnock, Bill Joy and John Doerr. Working first for Life Magazine, Menuez continued covering start-ups and established giants until the collapse of the dot.coms. This era was one of the most turbulent and significant--more jobs and wealth were created than ever before in human history.
Menuez' advertising campaigns for global brands include Chevrolet, Nikon, Siemens, Hewlett Packard, Northwest Airlines, Coca Cola, Nokia, and Microsoft. His work has been honored by many organizations, including the Kelly Awards, The AOP London, The Cannes Festival, The One Show, The Art Director's Club of NY, Photo District News, The Epson Creativity Award, American Photography, Graphis, and Communication Arts.
Menuez has had solo and group shows of his work in Milan, San Francisco, New York, Los Angeles and London. His most recent one-man shows include "Heaven, Earth, Tequila" at the Holbrook Arts Center, Millbrook, NY and "Transcendent Spirit" at Farmani Gallery, Los Angeles.
Menuez' work has also been featured in nine of the bestselling Day in the Life books, including the cover of A Day in the Life of Africa in 2002. In 1989, Menuez co-produced with David Elliott Cohen 15 Seconds: The Great California Earthquake of 1989, which raised over a half-million dollars for earthquake victims. In 1993, Menuez published Defying Gravity: The Making of Newton, Beyond Words Press, which was named one of the best 100 books of the past five years by Graphis. Recent books include Heaven, Earth, Tequila: Un Viaje al Corazón de México, Waterside Publishing, 2005, and Transcendent Spirit: The Orphans of Uganda, Beaufort Books, NY, 2008, with all proceeds to help Ugandan AIDS orphans. Menuez is currently working on a new book and documentary film, Fearless Genius: A Visual Memoir of Silicon Valley.
In 2009, Menuez formed Menuez Archive Projects, his exclusive boutique stock library featuring rights-managed images from his 30 years of award-winning imagery.
Menuez currently lives in New York City with his wife and son.
Text for Biographical Note from:
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doug_Menuez
www.menuez.com
http://dougmenuez.com/
Scope and Content
This collection consists of contact sheets, prints, slides, caption sheets, model releases, clippings, tear sheets, publications, portfolios and other material related to the photojournalism, documentary, commercial, and commissioned photography work of Doug Menuez.
Accessions 2004-060 and 2005-126 comprise Series 1. Silicon Valley Documentary. Series 1 contains prints, slides and contact sheets and is divided into two principal subseries: Jobs and Edits. Jobs are identified by the project or job name ( 24 Hours in Cyberspace, Adobe Systems, Apple Corporation, Against All Odds-One Digital Day, Defying Gravity: The Making of Newton, Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers, Newton, Next, Inc. and Farallon Computing). Subseries 2. Edits includes Silicon Valley and Reportage Selects removed from the Jobs subseries for editorial and other purposes.
This collection does not have a Series 2.
Negatives have been removed from Series 1. Jobs and filed in Series 3. Negatives (CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes). Please note that although Series 3. Negatives mirrors the structure of Series 1, not every negative has a corresponding print, slide or contact sheet. The scope and content field for most folders contains a complete list of the contact/negative roll numbers assigned by Menuez and his staff.
Series 4. Electronic Media consists of 5 CD-ROMs and 1 hard drive and is CLOSED to researchers. Please note that electronic media may take between 2-4 weeks for reformatting. The images contained in the hard drive are available online via Image Gallery (http://collections.stanford.edu/images/bin/page?forward=home).
Series 5. Accessions 2006-207 and 2007-081 consists of contact sheets, slides, prints, negatives, caption sheets and notes and is arranged into 4 subseries: Jobs, Photo Shoots, Negatives and Tear Sheets. Subseries 1. Jobs is arranged alphabetically by company or project. The number of images in each project was provided by the donor and is an approximation only. Corresponding negatives have been removed for preservation purposes and can be found in Subseries 3. Negatives (CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes). Subseries 2. Photo Shoots is arranged alphabetically by subject. Negatives have been removed and stored in flat boxes for preservation purposes and are OPEN to research. Many negatives do not correspond to contact sheets and are occasionally unnumbered. Not all rolls of negatives are complete. Subseries 3. Negatives is CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes. Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 5, Subseries 1. Jobs and Series 1, Subseries 1. Jobs (for Farallon images). Subseries 4. Tear Sheets consists of 2 folders of tear sheets relating to commercial photography jobs.
Contact sheets and negatives relating to Go Corporation and Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen comprise Series 6. Accession 2008-118. The negatives are CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes.
Series 7. Accession 2008-179 is arranged into 4 subseries: Jobs, Portfolio, Publications and Tear Sheets and Prints. Subseries 1. Jobs consists of prints, contact sheets, transparencies, negatives and related material, such as caption sheets, model releases and correspondence, related to Menuez's photography jobs. Many of the photographs were commissioned for publication in Discover, USA Today, Time, Mac Week, Forbes, Fortune, US News and World Report, People, and others. Negatives have been separated and housed in flat boxes for preservation purposes, and are OPEN to researchers. Numbers of photographic materials by format are noted in scope and content notes of many folders, and are approximate. Subseries 2. Portfolio consists of a number of Menuez's professional portfolios and contains prints, negatives and slides. Subseries 3. Publications and Tear Sheets contains examples of Doug Menuez's photography in printed publications, including tear sheets, advertisements, magazines, annual reports, brochures, etc. Subseries 4. Prints contains prints related to Menuez's documentary photography jobs, photo shoots and photo essays.
Series 8. Accession 2011-132 is arranged into 2 subseries: Jobs and Jobs - Computer Media. Subseries 1. Jobs consists of slides, negatives and contact sheets of Menuez's commercial work. Subseries 2. Jobs - Computer Media consists of CDs (97) that have been removed from Subseries 1. Jobs for preservation purposes. The CDs are CLOSED to researchers and may require 2-4 weeks for reformatting.
Series 9. Accession 2012-123 consists of one folder of 35mm slides.
Bibliography
Published works by Menuez, or publications containing work by menuez:
Drag Meet: 1996. Sears Point Race Track, California. Amateur drag racers. Offset printing, edition of 500.
Facetime. 2006, Woodstock (NY). Various portraits, including: Robert Redford, Francis Ford Coppola, Bob Weir, Sonia Braga, Martin Cruz Smith, Delroy Lindo, Natasha Richardson, and others. Indigo printing, edition of 100.
Heaven, Earth, Tequila: un viaje al corazón de México. Photographs by Douglas Menuez; introduction by Victor Villaseñor; text by Doug Menuez with Andrés Zamudio. 141, [6] p.: ill. Waterside Press, Cardiff-by-the-Sea (CA), 2005. ISBN#: 0976680106
My Year in the Wilderness. 1996. A collection of images 1970-1996 taken in various locations, including: Brazil, Italy, France, China and Spain. Inkjet printing on watercolor paper. Edition of 10.
Transcendent Spirit: The Orphans of Uganda. Photographs by Douglas Menuez; introduction by Dame Elizabeth Taylor; text by Rachel Scheier. 151 p.: ill. Beaufort Books, New York, 2008. ISBN#: 9780825305856
A Day in the Life of Africa. David Elliot Cohen, Susan Wels and Lee Lieberman Foreword by Archbishop Desmond Tutu. 288 p.: ill., maps. Tides Foundation, San Francisco, 2002. ISBN#: 0971802106
Defying Gravity: The Making of Newton. Photographs by Doug Menuez; introduction by Paul Saffo; text by Marcos Kounalakis. 176 p.: ill. Beyond Words, Hillsboro (OR), 1993. ISBN#: 0941831949
:15: Fifteen Seconds: The Great California Earthquake of 1989. David Elliot Cohen; Douglas Menuez and Ron Tussy, Editors. 119 p., [1] p.: ill. The Tides Foundation, San Francisco, 1989. ISBN#: 1559630418
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in nine series based upon accessions, and have been further broken down into subseries, and, in Series 1, subsubseries. The arrangement of the collection is as follows:
Series 1. Silicon Valley Documentary 1988-2002
Subseries 1. Jobs
Subsubseries 1. 24 Hours in Cyberspace, 1988-2002
Subsubseries 2. Adobe Systems, 1988-1995
Subsubseries 3. Apple Computer, 1990-1997
Subsubseries 4. Against All Odds, One Digital Day, 1997
Subsubseries 5. Defying Gravity: The Making of Newton, 1993-1996
Subsubseries 6. Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers, 1992-1996
Subsubseries 7. Newton, 1992-1993
Subsubseries 8. Next, Inc., 1986-1991
Subsubseries 9. Farallon Computing, 1989-1991
Subseries 2. Edits
Subsubseries 1. Reportage Selects
Subsubseries 2. Silicon Valley Selects
Series 3. Negatives
Series 4. Electronic Media
Series 5. Accessions 2006-207 and 2007-081
Subseries 1. Jobs
Subseries 2. Photo Shoots
Subseries 3. Negatives
Subseries 4. Tear Sheets
Series 6. Accession 2008-118
Subseries 1. Jobs
Subseries 2. Selects
Subseries 3. Negatives
Series 7. Accession 2008-179
Subseries 1. Jobs
Subseries 2. Portfolio
Subseries 3. Publications and Tear Sheets
Subseries 4. Prints
Series 8. Accession 2011-132
Subseries 1. Jobs
Subseries 2. Jobs - Computer Media
Series 9. Accession 2012-123
Adobe Systems.; Apple Computer, Inc.; Brand, Stewart; Callaway Golf Co.; Charles Schwab Corporation.; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Cook, Scott; Coppola, Francis Ford, 1939-; Cray, Inc..; Crédit suisse.; Curchack, Fred; Doerr, John E.; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company.; Eastman Kodak Company.; Eastwood, Clint, 1930-; Eddie Bauer, Inc..; Farallon Computing (Firm); Feinstein, Dianne, 1933-; Ferraro, Geraldine; Gates, Bill, 1955-; General Electric Company.; General Motors Corporation. Chevrolet Motor Division.; GO Corporation.; Hewlett Packard Company; International Business Machines Corporation.; J.P. Morgan Chase & Co..; Jaguar Cars Ltd..; Joy, William N.; Kleiner, Perkins, Caulfield and Byers ;; Kounalakis, Markos; Lindo, Delroy, 1952-; McNealy, Scott; Miller, Greg; Mullarkey, Karen, 1942-; NetObjects, Inc..; NeXT Computer, Inc..; Pacific Gas and Electric Company.; Perot, H. Ross, 1930-; QVC (Firm).; Reebok International Ltd..; Saffo, Paul; Sapient Corporation.; Sculley, John; Seybold, Jonathan; Smith & Hawken.; Smolan, Rick; Sun Microsystems; Warnock, John, 1940-; Wells, Fargo & Company.; Wozniak, Steve, 1950-; Computer software industry--United States--Photographs; Photojournalism; Photonegatives; Photoprints.; Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara County, Calif.); Science--History.; Transparencies.
- Series 1. Silicon Valley Documentary, 1988-2002; 16.75 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains prints, slides and contact sheets relating to Menuez's documentary work in Silicon Valley. This series is arranged by project or job name, which in most cases is the corporate entity documented. Corresponding negatives to many (but not all) of the prints, slides and contact sheets are present in Series 3, Negatives (closed to researchers).
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    This subseries contains contact sheets, slides and prints relating to Menuez's work documenting Silicon Valley corporations. Corresponding negatives to many, but not all contact sheets found in this subseries can be found in Series 3. Negatives.
    - Subsubseries 1. 24 Hours in Cyberspace, 1988-2002
      24 Hours in Cyberspace, 1996
      24 Hours in Cyberspace, 1996 is a compilation of images taken by the world's top photojournalists. Doug Menuez was one of 150 photographers who captured images documenting the effects of digital technology on people across the globe. The project constituted a photographic "freeze frame"; all images were all taken and submitted on February 8, 1996. Menuez's contributions included photographs of Greg Miller "11 year old software mogul," Netscape co-founder Marc Andreesen, and INTUIT co-founder Scott Cook.
      - 24 Hours in Cyberspace S-06, 35 mm. slides: color (Box 30, Folders 1-3)
    - Subsubseries 2. Adobe Systems, 1988-1995
      This subsubseries consists of contact sheets, slides and prints. Corresponding negatives are located in Series 3. Negatives (CLOSED to researchers).
      Adobe Systems
      The San Jose (Calif.) based Adobe Systems was founded in 1982 by John Warnock and Charles Geschke. Adobe reached national prominence in 1985 when it licensed its PostScript software to Apple. In the late 1980s the company specialized in digital fonts. Doug Menuez documented life at Adobe between 1988 and 1995, a time-span that included the launching of Adobe Photoshop and the early development of PDF (Portable Document Format).
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [1 of 7] 1988 Aug. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Contact sheets: 15294-16844
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [2 of 7] 1988 Aug. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 2)
        Contact sheets 16845-18150
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [3 of 7] 1988 Sept. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Contact sheets 01707-01709, 19404-19409
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [4 of 7] 1988 Sept. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Contact sheets 19410-19416
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [5 of 7] 1988 Oct. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Contact sheets 04157-04161, 02762-02763
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [6 of 7] 1988 Dec. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Contact sheets 08345, 08437-08441, 08979-08988
      - Adobe Binder no. 1 [7 of 7] 1988 Dec. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 7)
        Contact sheets 09149-09156, 09229-09232
      - Adobe #1 Binder [1 of 8] 1989 Jan. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 8)
        Contact sheets 11577-11581
      - Adobe #1 Binder [2 of 8] 1989 Mar. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Contact sheets 15340-15342, 16769-16770
      - Adobe #1 Binder [3 of 8] 1989 June S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 10)
        Contact sheets 26786-26787, 27138-27139, 27144-27146
      - Adobe #1 Binder [4 of 8] 1989 July S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Contact sheets 27863-27872
      - Adobe #1 Binder [5 of 8] 1989 Aug. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 12)
        Contact sheet 32405
      - Adobe #1 Binder [6 of 8] 1989 Oct. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 13)
        Contact sheets 0035-0041
      - Adobe #1 Binder [7 of 8] 1989 Dec. 12 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Contact sheets 8073-8078
      - Adobe #1 Binder [8 of 8] 1989 Dec. 12 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Contact sheets 8087-8098
      - Adobe Color Binder [1 of 3] 1990, Contact sheets: color (Box 1, Folder 16)
        Contact sheets 1000-1011
      - Adobe Color Binder [2 of 3] 1990, Contact sheets: color (Box 2, Folder 1)
        Contact sheets 42264-42267, 42277, 42423
      - Adobe Color Binder [3 of 3] 1990, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: color (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Adobe Annual #1 [1 of 3] 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 3)
        Contact sheets 8941-8958
      - Adobe Annual #1 [2 of 3] 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Contact sheets 8975, 9004-9020
      - Adobe Annual #1 [3 of 3] 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Contact sheets 9021-9038
      - Adobe Annual #2 [1 of 2] 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 6)
        Contact sheets 9043-9059, 9062-9065, 9117-9123
      - Adobe Annual #2 [2 of 2] 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Contact sheets 9124-9129, 63476-63485, 63512-63519
      - Adobe Annual #3 1990 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Contact sheets 8217-8219, 8472-8475, 8477, 8551-8558, 8682-8686, 8940
      - Adobe 1991, Binder no. 1 [1 of 3] 1991 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Contact sheets 9506-9507, 9518-9530, 9440-9443, 9633-9640
      - Adobe 1991, Binder no. 1 [2 of 3] 1991 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Contact sheets 9641-9650, 68953-68954, 68956-68961, 71122-71130
      - Adobe 1991, Binder no. 1 [3 of 3] 1991 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Contact sheets 71131, 72185-72189, 72627-72636
      - Adobe 1991, Binder no. 2 1991 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 2, Folder 12)
        Contact sheets 73029, 73031-73036
      - Adobe 1992, Binder no. 1 [1 of 2] 1992 Aug. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 1)
        Contact sheets 78411-78430, 8138-8143
      - Adobe 1992, Binder no. 1 [2 of 2] 1992 Aug. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 2)
        Contact sheets 8144-8151, 81801-81821, 8123-81824
      - Adobe 1994, Binder no. 11994 July 8 S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white and 24 x 28 cm.: color (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Rolls 1-18
      - Adobe 1995 (Seattle), no. 11995 Oct. S-01, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white and 24 x 28 cm.: color (Box 3, Folder 4)
        Contact sheets 07393-07399
      - Adobe, Work Prints #1 [1 of 3] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 4, Folder 1)
      - Adobe, Work Prints #1 [2 of 3] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 4, Folder 2)
      - Adobe, Work Prints #1 [3 of 3] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 4, Folder 3)
      - Adobe, Work Prints #2 [1 of 2] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 5, Folder 1)
      - Adobe, Work Prints #2 [2 of 2] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 5, Folder 2)
      - Adobe, Final Prints [1 of 2] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 5, Folder 3)
      - Adobe, Final Prints [2 of 2] S-01, Prints: 50 x 80 cm.: black and white (Flat-box 5, Folder 4)
    - Subsubseries 3. Apple Computer, 1990-1997
      This subsubseries consists of contact sheets and prints documenting various Apple-related Menuez projects, including the Super Mac, New Mac, Blue Print and Apple Rock Science. Corresponding negatives are located in Series 3. Negatives (CLOSED to researchers).
      Apple Computer
      The now mythical history of Apple Computer began with the release of the Steve Wozniak's Apple I in 1976. The company went public in 1980 following the release of the Apple III. The early 1980s saw a variety of growing pains which the company addressed by hiring PepsiCola's John Sculley as CEO. In 1985 Apple laid off nearly one fifth of its work force in 1985. Also during this time Sculley and Microsoft's Bill Gates became embroiled in a debate over the introduction of Windows 1.0, which had many similarities to the Mac GUI. By the time Doug Menuez came to Apple in 1990, the company had secured its niche market and once again become profitable. More than 9,000 people worldwide were on the Apple payroll.
      - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [1 of 3] 1995 Oct. S-03, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 5)
        Contact sheets 8853, 8855, 8578-8587
      - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [2 of 3] 1995 Oct. S-03, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 6)
        Contact sheets 8858-8592, 8842-8865
      - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [3 of 3] 1995 Oct. S-03, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 7)
        Contact sheets 8866-8874, 64877-64899
      - Apple 1992, no. 1 [1 of 2] 1995 Oct. S-03, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 8)
        Contact sheets 78440, 78447-78456, 8427-8428
      - Apple 1992, no. 1 [2 of 2] 1995 Oct. S-03, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 9)
        Contact sheets 78431-78446
      - Apple Super Mac 1993 Jan, Contact sheets: 28 x 21 cm. and 28 x 24 cm.: black and white (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Contact sheets 5401-5406, 63431, 63441, 63443, 63448, 63453, 63453A
      - New Mac, Binder no. 1 [1 of 2] 1997 July S-03, Contact sheets: 22 x 30 cm.: black and white (Box 6, Folder 1)
        Rolls 1-23